(走过的路)
我们是一条船上的
We're in this together.
不
No!
你体内偷来的能量还好吗
How's that, um, stolen grace inside you working out?
这可是该隐的血印
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
这么强大的魔法是有代价的
Magic that powerful comes at a price,
现在  我们还不知道这代价是什么
and right now we don't know what that price is.
把刀放下
Drop the blade.
我一碰到那把刀...
First time I touched that blade,
我就知道没人能阻止我了
I knew that I wouldn't be stopped.
我开始觉得那把刀还有其他的影响了
I'm starting to think the blade is doing something to you.
不
No!
睁开你的双眼  迪恩
Open your eyes, Dean.
我们一起对月长啸吧
Let's go take a howl at that moon.
(如今)
我听到传言了
I ard the rumors.
但我不相信
I said, "No, that can't be.
温家人会变成我们的一员
A Winchester one of us?"
但这是真的 是吗
But it's true, isn't it?
不管你曾经有怎样的灵魂
Whatever soul you had,
不管你曾经坚守过怎样的信条
whatever boy scout code you cuddled up to at night,
那些都没了
it's all gone.
剩下了什么
Leaving what?
看看你啊
Look at you.
克劳利在哪
Where is Crowley?
去死吧
Eat me.
我再问一次
One more time.
克劳利在哪
Where is Crowley?
-我哥哥在哪  -我不知道
- Where's my brother? - I don't know!
那就叫个知道的人来
Then you're gonna call somebody who does.
没人知道
No one knows!
他们都不回应
T-they won't answer!
-召唤他们  -我们有命令
- Make the call. - We're under orders!
召唤他们
Make the call!
求你了
Please.
我哥哥在哪
Where's my brother?!
[邪恶力量 第10季第1集]
(四周后)
好的  那么没有明显的作物枯萎
Right, right. So, no noticeable crop failures,
没有大规模牲畜死亡  什么都没有
no mass cattle deaths... nothing?
没有  没有任何动静  没有什么新事件
No. Nothing new on the radar. Nothing on the scope.
要我说这是好事
I'd say that's a good thing.
当然了  说得对
No, yeah, yeah, yeah. You're right.
谢了  麦克
I-I hear you, Mike. Thanks.
这的确是好事
That is a good thing.
好了
All right.
如果有什么异常情况及时通知我
Well, keep me posted if anything does pop up.
好  自己保重  萨姆
All right, watch yourself, Sam.
嗯  我会的
Yeah, I will. You got it.
谢了
Thanks.
(萨姆  放手吧)
(俄亥俄州失踪男子威斯康辛州被杀)
(萨姆来电)
萨姆  喂
Sam. Hello.
我可能有发现
I think I might've found something.
太好了
Oh, good.Good.
小卡  在听吗
Cass? You there?
我没事  我没事
It's okay. I'm... I'm okay.
接着说
Uh, go... go on.
听我说
Okay, get this.
威斯康辛州一名一周前被杀的无名男子
A John Doe who was murdered in wisconsin a week ago
其实是北俄亥俄州
turns out to be this guy named Drew Neely
一个宗教团体的失踪成员  名叫德鲁·尼利
who went missing from some religious order in northern Ohio, okay?
嗯
Yeah.
德鲁·尼利已经失踪3年了
Now, Drew Neely has been missing for three years.
他杀了妻子  孩子
Killed his wife, his kids,
随后人间蒸发
and...just disappeared.
我知道线索不多
I know it's thin...
但如果这人是被附身了
...but if this guy was possessed...
那么他就是第一个...
Well, that would make him the first...
第一个线索  我们已经很久没有...
The first lead, the first anything we've seen in...
抱歉
Sorry.
那个  这样吧
Actually, you know what?
我又仔细看了看报道
Now that I'm looking at this more,
我可能是
I-I think I, uh...
太心急了
I think I jumped the gun here, buddy.
不  萨姆  你说是条线索的
No, Sam, you said it was something.
嗯
Yeah.
应该不是
Uh, it's... it's not.
我想错了  抱歉
I was wrong. Sorry.
-我能帮忙  -小卡
- I can help. - Cass.
我们试过了
We tried that.
萨姆  你不能把那个恶魔伤你肩的事怪在我头上
Sam, you can't blame what that demon did to your shoulder on... on me.
-你当时...  -我没有
- You were out of... - I'm not, okay?
我没有怪你什么
I'm not blaming anything on you.
那事就是那样了
What happened...happened.
而且
And...
你该担心自己的健康了
You need to be worrying about yourself.
我真的不该来打扰你
I-I really shouldn't have bothered you.
你还好吗  萨姆
How are you, Sam?
我挺好的  我没事
I'm good. I-I'm all right.
我就是挺累的
I'm just tired, you know?
如果能把他找回来  我就会没事了
I'll be better when we get him back...
不过我要先收拾他一顿
A-after I kick his butt.
我好想他
I miss him.
是啊
Yeah.
他为什么就那么一走了之呢
Why would he just disappear?
或许那不是他的选择
Who says he had a choice?
那字条是谁写的
Well, then who wrote the note?
你觉得可不可能
You think there's any chance...
迪恩可不可能还是...
Any chance at all that Dean is still...
还是原来的那个迪恩吗
Still even remotely Dean?
∮ 我性感得没法爱 ∮
∮ I'm too sexy for my love, too sexy for my love. ∮
∮ 爱情要弃我而去了 ∮
∮ Love's going to leave me. ∮
∮ 我性感得衣服装不下 ∮
∮ And I'm too sexy for my shirt, too sexy for my shirt. ∮
∮ 性感得疼 ∮
∮ So sexy it hurts. ∮
∮ 连米兰都被我性感得受不了 ∮
∮ And I'm too sexy for Milan, too sexy for Milan. ∮
∮ 还有纽约和日本 ∮
∮ New York and Japan. ∮
-关掉吧  -下去吧
- Turn if off! - Get off the stage!
大家一起唱
Everybody!
好吧
Okay.
几点了
What time is it?
如果我又休息超时了  达瑞尔非杀了我不可
Darryl's gonna kill me if I'm late from my break again.
该死
Damn!
我叫你赶紧点的
I told you to hurry it up.
但你非得做那个
But then you had to go and do that thing with the...thing.
就是你求着我做的那个吗
Oh, you mean that thing that you were begging me for?
我就是求你快点吧
Begging you to hurry it up, maybe.
做得那么爽就别再争论了
Well, let's not argue about good sex.
的确很爽  是吧
It was good, wasn't it?
不过  别乐过头了
Just, uh...don't get too excited, you know?
别爱上我了
Or...too attached.
我就是路过这儿罢了
'cause I'm just rollin' through.
其实这话可以说得更好听的
You know, there's about a million other ways you could have said that.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
你觉得呢
What's it look like?
在我的床上搞
In my bed?
什么
What?
还真是
Oh, yeah.
混蛋
Jerk.
贱人
Bitch.
你俩开房去吧
Get a room, you two.
开过了  但被你俩玷污了
Had a room till you two soiled it.
爱你哦  克劳利
Love you, Crowley.
更爱你  亲爱的
Love you more, sweetheart.
是安·玛丽  混蛋
Anne Marie, Jackass.
我知道
Knew that.
请穿裤子
Pants?
三局两胜
Best of three.
输家买酒
Losers buy the beer.
买很多酒
Lots of beer.
那姑娘不错啊
Girl seemed nice.
受过些伤
Slightly damaged.
看得出以前的你有点为此动心了
I could see the old you falling for that.
别担心
Yeah, well, not to worry.
她对我毫无意义
She means nothing.
那就好
Good, good.
因为我们
'cause you and I,
我们是人过不留痕
we're rolling stones.
不能有牵挂
No distractions.
守住  守住
Lock it down. Lock it down.
-闭嘴吧  -你要丢球了
- Stop talking. - You're bodging it!
你就非得说话
If you'd shut up...
你老这么唠叨我都没法玩了
Keep talking... I can't play the game.
我们谈谈嘛  走吧
Come on, we'll talk about it. Let's go.
跟我走
Come on. Let's go.
等着我
Hang on.
放开我
Get off me.
你为什么这么对我
Why are you doing this to me?!
你得冷静下来
You need to calm down.
-你去哪了  -住手
- Where were you? - Stop it!
是他吗
Hey, is this him?
有什么问题吗
There a problem?
你是马特吗
Yeah, are you Matt?
迪恩
Dean!
你给我滚得远远的
You need to get away from here.
再也别联系她
Don't try and contact her.
连想都不要想她
In fact, don't even think about her.
听懂了吗
You understand me?!
等一下
Just a moment.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
汉娜
Hannah.
我感觉到了一丝尴尬
I'm sensing awkwardness.
没有领袖了吗
So...there's no... no leader?
你们在自我管理
You're governing yourselves?
差不多吧
Mostly.
举行了很多重建  重组的会议
There's lot of meeting on rebuilding and reorganization...
做了大量的和解
lots of reconciliation.
梅塔特隆呢
And Metatron?
还在监狱里
Still in jail.
他的门已经永久封住了
His door has been made permanent.
我以为能早点见到你呢
I would've thought we'd see you sooner.
我也想早点去  但是
I would've come sooner but...
我很高兴你没有
I'm glad you didn't.
是这样  我
You see, I...
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
天堂需要你的帮助
Heaven needs your help.
说吧
Anything.
大部分坠落的天使都已经回到了天堂
Most of the angels who fell during the fall have returned to heaven.
还有少数没有
A few have not.
有些是不肯回去
Some out-and-out refuse.
叛逃了
Rogues.
其中两个杀了我们的兄弟
Two of them have killed one of our own
那个天使只是想带他们回家
for only attempting to bring them back home.
是谁
Who were they?
丹尼尔和阿迪娜
Daniel and Adina.
得找到他们
They must be found.
他们必须被带回家
They must be brought home,
并受到责罚  这是为了所有人
and they must be punished for the sake of all.
你能帮我吗
Will you help me?
当然
Yes.
谢谢你能赶来  探员
Appreciate you coming down, agent.
但我们怕是浪费国家汽油了
But I'm afraid you may have just cost uncle Sam a tank of gas.
怎么说
Oh, why's that?
你是来调查德鲁·尼利的案子  对吗
You came up here to investigate Drew Neely's murder, right?
嗯
Right.
问题是  没人能确定那是桩凶杀案
Problem is, no one's certain it was a murder at all.
那是什么情况
Okay, then what are we dealing with here?
自杀吗
A suicide?
应该说是自卫
Self-defense, more likely.
监控录像有点问题
Uh, the surveillance footage was corrupted.
我们的技术人员终于修复了文件
Our techies finally managed to clean up the file.
等一下
Hold on a sec now.
(黑马刺)
我们可以按照你的意思来
We can do this however you want.
别装作我下午没看着你
Don't pretend I didn't see you this afternoon.
你看清楚我的招式了吗
Did you get a good look? You see my moves?
希望如此  我正想找个厉害的练练拳脚
I hope so, 'cause I sure could use the competition.
盯住那个不明男子
That John Doe right there is the one you want to keep your eye on.
该死
Son of a bitch.
看
Watch.
你们这些阿比顿的粉丝都一个样
Well, all you Abaddon groupies are the Same, you know that?
你  还有在加油站袭击我的那个混蛋
You, the douche that jumped me at the gas station,
就是不肯接受女王已经驾崩  是吗
You can't just can't accept that the queen is dead, can you?
或许我们不能接受的
Maybe we just can't accept
是杀了她的是你这样的混蛋
that a douche like you was the one who killed her.
是啊  这真是不好受  是吧
Yeah, that's got to hurt, doesn't it?
那个黄书男也没招谁惹谁
Okay, now, porn guy's just minding his own business.
德鲁·尼利来了
And there's Drew Neely.
看见刀了吗
See the knife?
嗯
Yeah.
这就算是伤人企图
That's intent right there.
看好了
Now watch this.
好像是把短剑
Looks like a cutlass or something.
我也不知道这算怎么回事
I don't know what the hell this is.
问题是  我不知道这人是好人还是疯子
Problem is, we don't know if this guy's a hero or a psychopath.
这张图片已经上传通报了
That's the image that's getting uploaded to the wires.
警探  你介意我  再仔细看看吗
Detective, do you mind if I, uh, take another look at this?
自便吧
Knock yourself out.
-我就回来  -嗯
- See you back in a few. - Right.
传真  爸爸
Fax, dad.
谁来的  伙计
Who's it from, buddy?
没说  只有张照片
Doesn't say. There's a picture.
谢了  伙计
Thanks a lot, bud.
是他吗
Is it him?
(没错)
我都不知道天使也会晕车呢
I didn't know angels could get nauseous.
我只是需要缓缓
I just need a moment.
都怪我  我过弯道时再开快点
It's my fault. I'll take the curves faster.
你呢  卡西迪奥
And you, Castiel?
你还好吗
You're feeling well?
嗯
Oh, yes.
好得不得了
Like a million dollars.
不是这样的
That's not true.
对我来说是的
It's my truth.
你离开天堂后  你借来的能量就渐渐枯竭
When you left heaven, your borrowed grace was failing.
看来  你现在情况更糟了
By the looks of you, you've only gotten worse.
我没事
I'm fine.
你要死了  卡西迪奥
You're dying, Castiel.
你需要更多能量
You need more grace.
而我们有任务要执行
And we have a mission in front of us
所以我的需求  我们所有人的需求都得等等了
that supersedes my needs... all of our needs.
你说呢
Don't you agree?
你是个好士兵  汉娜
You're a good soldier, Hannah...
最优秀的之一
And one of the best.
如果不是你勇敢出手  梅塔特隆是绝不会
Metatron certainly could not have been brought to heel
被制服的
without your bravery.
你也功不可没
Or yours.
你得照顾好自己  卡西迪奥
You must take care of yourself, Castiel.
那么为了我活命  就该让别的天使死掉吗
And another angel should die so that I can be saved?
这有那么难想通吗
Is this really that hard to understand?
汉娜
Hannah.
我现在好多了
I'm feeling better now.
嗯
Oh, yeah.
那个黄书男真不是人
Porn guy was an animal.
那人突然就上去袭击他
Bro came at him like, "What?!"
他则淡定得很
And he was all like, "Wh-a-a-at?"
"叫我的名字  叫我的名字
"Say my name! Say my name!
叫我的名字"
Say my name."
流了好多血啊
And there was a lot of blood.
这样啊
Right.
那个人
When the guy, uh... when...
就是
When...
"黄书男"进来的时候  他说什么了吗
"Porn guy" came in, did he...say anything?
"黄书在哪"
"W-where's the porn""
就这句
That's all he said?
他买什么了吗
Did he buy anything?
他用信用卡了吗
Did he... did he use a credit card?
没有吗
Nothing?
那么有个人走进来
So some guy comes in,
在你店里  在你眼前杀了另一个人
kills another guy in your store on your watch,
你就像没事人一样该咋咋地吗
and you just... You what? Just keep on keepin' on?
你是说那个黄书男把另一个人捅死
You mean when porn guy was stabbing the other guy to death
而且他们就在我10英尺开外处
10 feet in front of me,
我都拉在
and I was having a total code-brown moment
我最喜欢的裤子里了
in my favorite freakin' pants
因为我以为接下来会是我的时候
because I thought I was next,
我有没有上去采访他一番吗
did I conduct a field interview?
没有
No.
能帮我个忙吗
Oh, hey. Uh, can you do me a solid?
在货架下捡到的
Found this wedged under the T.P.
大概是那个死者的手机
I think it's the dead guy's phone,
如果你要回警局去
and, uh, if you're heading back to the station...
(电子邮件: 老大 有任务给你)
(温彻斯特  威斯康辛州  阿姆赫斯特  加油站  11点到12点  阿比顿万岁)
你已经死了啊
You're dead.
没有
Nope.
只是在用死人的手机
Just using a dead man's phone.
小鹿  你好久才找到我们啊
Moose. Took you long enough.
我和你哥哥都寻思你是不是又撞狗了
Your brother and I were beginning to wonder if you'd hit another dog.
你懂的
You know?
我哥哥死了  克劳利
My brother is dead, Crowley.
我知道你找了个恶魔放进了他身体里
I know you have some freaking demon parading around in his meatsuit,
相信我  你会为此付出代价的
And trust me, you are gonna pay for that.
小鹿  小鹿
Moose. Moose.
恐怕你是梦想得不够大胆
I'm afraid you haven't allowed yourself to dream quite big enough here.
你哥哥生龙活虎呢  多亏了血印
Your brother is very much alive, courtesy of the mark.
迪恩体内唯一的恶魔
And the only demonized soul inside of Dean
就是他自己
is his and his alone.
虽然有点扭曲
Wee bit more twisted,
毁坏得有点认不出来
a little more mangled beyond human recognition,
但我可以向你保证  那是他自己的灵魂
but, I can assure you, all his.
好了  感觉好点了吗
There, now. Feel better?
还有  你不断派去杀我哥哥的
And the, uh, Abaddon supporters you've been sending
阿比顿追随者
to kill my brother,
迪恩被骗了是什么感觉
how does Dean feel about that double-cross?
假如你以为是这么回事
If that's what you think is happening,
那比我想的还不自量力
then you're more out of your depths than I thought.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you did this,
我不知道你玩的是什么黑魔法
What kind of... black-magic stunt you pulled,
但你给我听好了
but hear me --
我会救回我哥哥的
I will save my brother
至死方休
or die trying.
你知道整件事最让我兴奋的地方在哪吗
You know what tickles me about all this?
就是真正让你受不了的事
It's what's really eating you up.
你不在乎他是恶魔
You don't care that he's a demon.
你也当过恶魔
Heck, you've been a demon.
我们都当过恶魔
We've all been demons.
不是的  而是他和我在一起了
No, it's that he's with me
而他开心得要死
and he's having the time of his life.
你不能接受的是  他现在属于我
You can't stand the fact that he's mine.
他不是你的宠物
He's not your pet.
我的宠物
My pet?
他是我的死党
He's my best friend,
我的犯罪搭档
my partner in crime.
人们会为我们写赞歌  画漫画的
They'll write songs about us, graphic novels.
《克劳力和松鼠的悲惨历险记》
"The Misadventures of Crowley and Squirrel".
迪恩·温彻斯特让我完整
Dean Winchester completes me,
正是这一点让你不淡定了
and that's what makes you lose your chickens.
我会找到你
I am going to find you,
我会救回我哥哥
I am going to save my brother,
然后  我要把你碎尸万段
and then I'm going to kill you dead.
这是行话  是吧
Well, that's the operative phrase, isn't it?
"找到你"
"Find you."
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
(已定位)
(北达科他州  比乌拉)
(黑马刺  北达科他州  比乌拉  刀河路156号)
丹尼尔
Daniel.
你在钓什么呢
What are you fishing for?
主要是鳟鱼
Trout, mostly.
它们喜欢香喷喷的长卷尾蛆饵
They do love a good curlytail grub.
窍门是找准急流外的那个特殊位置
Trick is to find that special spot just outside the run,
那些大鱼
where the big ones --
聪明的鱼在那儿藏身
the smart ones -- are holding low.
它们...会挣扎吗
Do they -- do they put up much of a fight?
你是说那些真正渴望自由的吗
The ones who truly want to be free?
它们会抗争的
They do.
你是为了我们死去的兄弟而来
You're here about our brother who died.
你很吃惊吗
Does that surprise you?
我可以向你保证...
I can assure you...
假如他不来招惹我们  本不会有人受伤
Had he just left us alone, no one would've been harmed.
他得到的命令是不能放任你们不管
His orders were to not leave you alone.
而你杀了他
And you killed him.
然后天堂又派了两个人下来
And heaven sends two more.
我们天使兄弟们怎么就是不明白呢
What is it about us angels that we can't seem to get the message?
或许是你不明白吧
Perhaps it is you who has failed to get the message?
我们所有人都要服从天堂的命令
All of us serve at heaven's command.
我想是吧
I suppose.
但那是在大坠落之前  不是吗
But that was before the fall, wasn't it?
你是一名天使  永远都是
You are an angel, once and forever.
在不知情的情况下
Dropped unwillingly...
被迫
unknowingly...
坠落到一片陌生的土地
into a strange land,
而我们发现  这是一片
a land that, as it turns out,
崇尚自由  个体的土地
celebrates the free, the individual.
这是几千年来第一次
For the first time in thousands of years,
我有了选择
I have choices.
而随着每一次选择...
And with each choice...
-我开始发掘真实的自我  -太胡扯了
- I begin to discover who I really am. - This is nonsense.
就因为天堂没教过这个吗
Because they don't teach you this in heaven?
也许他们该教
Perhaps they should.
那你就会明白这为什么值得为之斗争了
Then you would understand why it's worth fighting for.
他在嘲笑我们
He's taunting us.
那又怎样
And then what?
杀了他吗
We kill him?
还是他杀了我们
Or he kills us?
我们有命令
There are orders.
我们也有时间
And there is time.
继续听这些废话吗
To hear more of this?
有时间劝他做正确的事
To convince him to do the right thing.
而且  汉娜
Besides, Hannah,
我们还不知道另一个在哪
we still don't even know where the other one is...
那个女人
the woman.
你们得待到日落时分
You'll have to stay for sunset.
这里的夜晚令人醍醐灌顶
Nighttime around here is a revelation.
是你派了那些恶魔来杀我
You sent those demons to kill me?
是为了让你保持警惕
To keep you sharp.
是吗
Really?
如果不是我派恶魔一路跟着你
If it wasn't for me throwing demon chum your way,
你觉得会怎样
what do you think would've happened?
血印需要血祭
The mark needs to be sated.
-否则  -否则我就会变成恶魔
- Otherwise... - Otherwise, I turn into a demon.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
这点我六周前就明白了
I sort of got that six weeks ago.
我只是想帮忙
Just trying to help.
你骗了我
You lied.
你以为我是谁
Who do you think you're talking to here?
绿野仙踪里诚实的铁皮人啊
Does the tin man have a sheet-metal willy?
我当然会骗人
Of course I lied.
好吧
Okay.
坐下
Sit down.
坐嘛
Sit.
为了咱们的未来  我必须让你振作
I needed to keep you sharp for our future,
咱们还得聊聊未来
about which we need to talk.
咱们的未来
Our future?
职业方面的未来
Our professional future.
怎么说呢
How to put this?
如果要我再多忍受
If I have to spend one more night
哪怕一天你自怨自艾的情绪
in this fetid petri dish of broken dreams and B.O.,
我都宁愿自杀
I will cut off my own face.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我没事
'cause I'm good.
我好得很
Hell, I'm great.
是吗
Really?
你还能吃多少次"自杀式鸡翅挑战"
How many suicide wings can you eat?
你还要唱多少次卡拉OK
How many one-hit wonders can you karaoke to death?
好吧  本来说好
Okay, see, the deal was
我们要对月嗥叫
we howl at the moon...
不分时间  永不停下
No time stamp, no expiration date.
我们已经叫过了
We've howled.
也吠过了
We've bayed.
什么好玩的我们都玩过三遍了
W-we've done extraordinary things to triplets,
一切都非常爽
all of which have been massively entertaining.
我会永远珍惜这段日子的网络相册
I will treasure our flickr albums forever.
可现在该接受我们的真实面目
But now it's time for us to accept what we are
回去工作了
and go back to work.
不了
Pass.
好好想想
Think of it...
地狱之王  有迪恩·温彻斯特相助
The king of hell, Dean Winchester by his side.
我们一起统治  一起创建完美的地狱
Together we rule. Together we create the perfect hell.
我们之间萌生的友谊  永远不会结束
And all of this that's bloomed between us never ends.
我们并不是要结束狂欢
We're not ending the party.
只是换个地方继续
We're just moving the party.
离开小俱乐部  换成露天体育场巡演
Out with the club circuit, in with the stadium tour.
我是不是忘了说  我之前跟小鹿通过话
Did I forget to mention I spoke to moose earlier?
什么
What?
是的
Yes.
显然  他追踪我们有一段日子了
Apparently, he's been tracking us for some time now.
他从你捅死的那个恶魔的手机上
He got my text from the cell of that demon
找到了我的短信
that you stabbed in blah, blah, blah.
真是
It was --
我们谈了心  感情涌动
words were spoken -- emotions.
回想一下  我意识到
I realize, in retrospect,
或许我们说了太多  情绪太激动了
perhaps too many words, too many emotions.
他追踪了电话
He traced the call.
我的错
My bad.
我猜他最晚明早就会赶到
I guess he'll be here by morning -- the latest.
你出卖了我
You sold me out.
真是太棒了
Well, that's just lovely.
我不知道你是怎么回事
I don't know what's going on with you.
我真的不知道
I truly don't.
可我真是受够了
But I've had just about enough of it.
出卖你
Sold you out?
说"帮你个忙"比较合适
Try "doing you a favor."
过去六个月我为你做的一切
Everything I've done for you for the past six months --
血印  第一刃  让你复生
the mark, the First Blade, midwifing you back to life,
让你做我的搭档
offering you a seat by my side --
都是在帮你  是馈赠
has been a favor, a gift,
不管你明不明白
whether you see it or you don't.
今晚好好想想
Take the night.
做出决定
Decide.
你知道哪能找到我
You know where to find me.
需要帮忙吗
Need some help?
我觉得是
Yeah. I -- I think so.
它突然罢工了
It just died on me.
-在这儿吗  -对
- Out here? - Yeah.
你的车真是想和你对着干啊
Your ride really has it out for you, huh?
我猜是
I guess so.
要我帮你吗
Give you a hand with that?
好  非常感谢  多谢
Yeah. Yeah, I'd appreciate it. Thanks.
这些靠计算机控制的新款车啊
These new cars and their computerized brains, huh?
放错一个零  整个都完蛋
One zero out of place, and the whole thing just goes kaput.
看那  问题就出在那儿
Well, right there. There's your problem.
那是什么东西
What the hell is that?
是个制动开关
Well, that's a kill switch.
遥控器在这儿
This here is the remote.
看来你是右撇子
Guessing you're a righty.
∮ 虚幻的爱人 ∮
∮ Imaginary lovers. ∮
∮ 不会拒绝你 ∮
∮ Never turn you down. ∮
-跑调了  -太难听了
- Tone deaf! - Awful!
够了
Enough!
∮ 当别人都弃你而去 ∮
∮ When all the others turn you away. ∮
∮ 她们还在你身边 ∮
∮ They're around. ∮
∮ 这是我独有的快乐 ∮
∮ It's my private pleasure. ∮
∮ 午夜幻想 ∮
∮ Midnight fantasy. ∮
你们真讨厌
You all suck.
喝吧  硬汉
Drink, tough guy.
不用  我没事
Nah, I'm good.
你自己作死了
Your funeral.
怎么了
What?
我们走吧  就我们俩
Let's go somewhere, you and me.
我们就在外面呢
We are somewhere.
不
No.
去别的地方
Somewhere else.
亲爱的
Sweetie...
我们都不怎么认识
we barely know each other.
你还喝醉了
And you're drunk.
是啊  不过
Yeah, but, uh...
我还维护过你呢  对吧
I-I protected your honor, didn't I?
是啊  我本来也这么想
Yeah. I thought so, too.
看你揍马特  我还好开心
Seeing you take on Matt, I was like, "wow""
从没有人为我做这种事
No one's ever done that for me before.
但你不停地揍他
But then you kept going and going,
我意识到不管你是怎么了
and I realized whatever is going on with you
你绝不是为了维护我
has nothing to do with my "honor" at all.
从一场酒吧斗殴里看出这么多来
You got all that from a bar fight?
你可真厉害
You're good.
我在旅馆当服务员
I wait tables at a roadhouse.
我遇到过坏人  遇到过好人
I meet the bad guys. I meet the good guys.
也许有那么一阵
And maybe for a second there,
我还认为你是假装坏人的好人
I though you were a good guy playing bad.
我不知道  这不重要
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
也许你只是
Maybe you're just --
开车经过每一个小镇破酒馆
The kind of guy who sleeps with every skank
都会和镇上的骚娘们上床的人吗
in every small-town dive that he passes through?
你还真是会看人
Well, you really do know how to read people,
因为这听起来就是我
'cause that sure as hell sounds like me.
瞧见没
Now, see?
我真是一团糟
I'm so screwed up myself
我会离开这里  还心想是我活该
I'm gonna walk out of here thinking I actually deserved that.
我无法理解的是
What I'll never understand Is
为什么天使不肯承认
why angels won't acknowledge
人间的智慧
the wisdom to be found down here.
人类能有什么智慧
What wisdom is to be gained from humans?
我不是在跟你说话
I'm not speaking to you.
你明白他在...
Do you understand what he's...
好吧
Fine.
即使你可以获得自由
But if you are to be free,
也得由所有天使来决定
that is to be decided by all angels.
这就是天使的讽刺啊
There's that angelic irony.
我们不会回去的
We're not going back there.
永远不会
Not ever.
阿迪娜
Adina.
这是汉娜和卡西迪奥
This is Hannah and Castiel.
请收起天使之刃
Stow the blade, please.
她先收起她的
When she stows hers.
汉娜  你在干什么
Hannah, what are you doing?
我们在监狱里是没有机会争取自由的
We'll never get a chance to argue our freedom from a prison cell.
你们屠杀同类之前  就该想到这一点
You should've thought of that before slaughtering one of your own.
不不  我们在谈话
No, no. We were talking.
我们刚刚有进展
We were getting somewhere.
-好了  各位  -你想要自由
- Okay, everybody just -- - You want to be free?
来啊  随意
Go ahead. Be free.
汉娜
Hannah.
住手
Stop this.
-不  -丹尼尔
- No. - Daniel.
不
No!
我们得抓住她
We have to get her.
她跑了
She's gone.
-必须抓住她  -汉娜
- We have to. - Hannah.
结束了
It's over.
我们走  我们走
Let's go. Let's go.
好了  甜蜜的家
Okay. Home, sweet home.
深呼吸
Breathe.
行了
There you go.
你还好吧  搭档
You good, partner?
你的小胳膊还好吗
How's that chicken wing?
你是谁
Who are you?
我第一次弄伤胳膊
First time I broke my arm,
那是我哥哥戴维
my older brother, Davey,
让我坐在他三速档自行车的把手上
had me riding on the handles of his three-speed.
做了个前轮离地的动作
Decided to pop us a wheelie,
想在DQ门外的小妞面前耍耍帅
look real fancy for all the little pretties outside the DQ.
虽然是帅了一小会儿
Well, we were looking mighty good for a little bit.
然后一声惊叫
And then, "Whoop"
火烧屁股了
ass end over teakettle, boy.
疼得要死
Hurt like a son of a bitch.
你是萨姆·温彻斯特
You're Sam Winchester.
我想这点我们都能确定
I think we both can agree on that.
而你的哥哥迪恩
And your older brother, Dean, well...
他和我  是老相识了
He and I, we go way back.
你是猎人吗
You're a hunter?
行啊
Sure.
就这么说吧
Yeah, we can go with that.
猎杀你哥哥也算是猎人吧
Hunting your brother counts, right?
是我的话  就不那么做
I wouldn't do that.
-是啊  -相信我
- Yeah. - Trust me.
听着  老兄  我不知道你是谁
Look, buddy, I-I don't know who you are, all right?
我不知道你想要什么或者我哥哥做了什么
I don't what you want or what my brother did,
但如果你还有理智
but if you got any sense,
我建议你快逃走  逃回那个...
I suggest you turn tail and run back to that
你从上面走下来的征兵广告
army recruiting ad that spit you out in the first place.
他是个禽兽
He's a monster.
是的
Well, he was.
他是
Yeah, he was...
很久很久以前
Many, many moons ago.
但现在  他是猎物
But now he's prey.
现在我是猛兽了
And I'm the monster now.
我们得上报这事
We have to report this.
说什么
And say what?
事情失去了控制吗
Things got out of control?
又一个天使死了
Another angel has died.
他想杀我  卡西迪奥
He was going to kill me, Castiel.
他们只是不想被打扰
They just wanted to be left alone.
没有规矩  就会混乱
Without rules, there is chaos.
混乱之中会产生像娜奥米  巴塞洛缪
Out of chaos rise angels like Naomi,
这样的天使
Bartholomew...
还有梅塔特隆
Metatron.
也许  我在这下面和他们待在一起太久了
Well, perhaps I've been down here with them for too long.
这世界似乎只有混乱
There's seemingly nothing but chaos.
但混乱并不只产生邪恶
But not all bad comes from it.
艺术
Art.
希望
Hope.
爱
Love.
梦想
Dreams.
但那些都是人类的
But t-those are human things.
是啊
Yes.
(萨姆来电)
酒吧的钱付了
I left you an open tab at the bar.
你尽管喝吧
Knock yourself out.
我可能还真会接受你的邀请呢
Well, hell, I just may take you up on that.
你是谁
And who is this?
我吗
Me?
我是报应
Well, I'm karma, brother.
拿着我弟弟的电话吗
On my brother's phone?
拿着你弟弟的电话
On your brother's phone.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
还没有
No. Not yet.
只要你去我指定的地方
And as long as you show up where I tell you to show up,
你弟弟就不会有事
your brother will be just fine.
我怎么确定他还活着
And how do I know he's still alive?
说话
Speak.
他还活着
Proof of life.
迪恩
Dean!
有笔吗
Got a pen?
不  你听我说
No, you listen to me.
没有交易
There's no trade.
没有见面  什么都没有
There's no meet-up. There's no nothing --
只有我百分之百地保证
Except the 100% guarantee that,
总有一天
somewhere down the road,
我会找到你  我会杀了你
I will find you, and I will kill you.
那对你死了的弟弟可起不了安慰作用
Well, that'll be cold comfort to your dead brother.
我都叫他放我走了
I told him to let me go.
所以他现在陷入的麻烦
So whatever jam he's in now,
就只是他的问题
that is his problem.
好的  我割开他喉咙时
Yeah, well, I'll be sure to pass that on to him
一定会转告他的
as I'm slitting his throat.
好  你请便  因为他了解我
Yeah, you do that, 'cause he knows me.
他也完全了解  如果说我有什么特点
And he knows damn sure that if I am one thing,
那就是信守承诺
I am a man of my word.